

Islom Pulatov

Phone: +1 510-766-8505 Email: islapulatov@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/islom-pulatov-

983057165/

Portfolio: https://portfolio-production-f5a1.up.railway.app/

Github: https://github.com/Islompulatov

About Me

Junior Data Scientist with strong critical thinking, mathematical foundation and programming skills. I have strong knowledge in data analytics, computational modelling and data visualization. Working for 1+ years with Python and solving realtime problems with machine learning and deep learning models.

Work Experience

Sep 2022 - Jan 2022 Internship Data Scientist at Data Glacier company

March 2018 - Oct 2018 Internship Automative Engineer in the factory ONIKS Tashkent

Apr 2016 - 2018 Math and Physics Tutor in Private Learning Center

Educational Background

Jan 2022- Nov 2022 Epicode School Data Scientist

Sep 2014 - June 2018 Tashkent State Technical Unversity I am holder of Automatical Engineering diploma

Languages

English - Advanced Russian- Advanced Uzbek - Native Polish - Beginner

Skills & Proficiencies

- Pvthon
- Pandas
- Numpy
- BeautifulSoup
- Selenium
- Matplotlib
- · Statistics
- Scikit-learn
- Pytorch
- OpenCV
- Streamlit
- Django
- SQL HTML
- CSS
- Docker PowerBl
- PostgreSQL
- Spark
- Hadoop

Certificates

- PostgreSQL Udemy Certificate:
- Epicode Graduation Certificate:
- Pirple- Python is easy:
- Strive School Python:
- Strive School-ML:
- Strive School DL:
- Strive School Software Engineering:
- Kaggle-Pandas:
- Kaggle Intro Machine Learning:
- Kaggle Intermediate Machine Learning:
- Kaggle Data Visuzalization: